<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Isagani Jaen</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Isagani Jaen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.125.4</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 01:43:46 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Meet ProdAI: My Open-Source AI Assistant</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/meet-prodai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 01:43:46 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/meet-prodai/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone!
I’m super excited to share something I’ve been working on – ProdAI, my very own open-source AI assistant. If you’ve ever wanted a handy AI buddy to help with your daily tasks, answer questions, or just have a chat, then you’re going to love this. Let me walk you through what ProdAI is, how it works, and how you can set it up for yourself.
Available at my Github repository: https://github.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Data Analyst to Leadership in Tech</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/from-data-analyst-to-leadership-in-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 17:59:05 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/from-data-analyst-to-leadership-in-tech/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: Hello 👋, and welcome to my blog! My name is Isagani Jaen, and I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share my journey with you. Through this blog, I aim to provide insights into my professional experiences, lessons learned, and expertise in the tech industry.
My Professional Journey: My journey in the tech world began on June 2012. Over the years, I&amp;rsquo;ve had the opportunity to work with some incredible teams and tackle a variety of projects that have shaped my skills and perspective.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resume/</guid>
      <description>Experience Software Development Senior Analyst Accenture in the Philippines Jun 2022 - Present · Worked directly with clients as GNR-Analytics Lead. · Applied innovative ideas to drive the automation of Delivery Analytics at the client level using technologies such as clients&#39; internal Business Intelligence Suite, Google&#39;s F1 Engine, Google SQL, Workflow Pipeline, Google App Scripts and performed data analysis using Python and Colab.
System Developer Analyst Accenture in the Philippines Oct 2020 - Jun 2022 · 1 yr 9 mos · Perfromed ETL, reports mobilization, dashboard creation, workflow automation, and reporting automation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/</guid>
      <description> Personal Website My online portfolio, isaganijaen.com was created using Hugo.
Visit Site ProdAI - AI Personal Assistant My AI personal assistant powered by Gemma 2B, Tailwind CSS, DaisyUI and VueJS.
Visit Repository </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
