<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Profile on Isagani Jaen</title>
    <link>https://isaganijaen.com/tags/profile/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Profile on Isagani Jaen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.125.4</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 17:59:05 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://isaganijaen.com/tags/profile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>From Data Analyst to Leadership in Tech</title>
      <link>https://isaganijaen.com/blog/from-data-analyst-to-leadership-in-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 17:59:05 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://isaganijaen.com/blog/from-data-analyst-to-leadership-in-tech/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: Hello , and welcome to my blog! My name is Isagani Jaen, and I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share my journey with you. Through this blog, I aim to provide insights into my professional experiences, lessons learned, and expertise in the tech industry.
My Professional Journey: My journey in the tech world began on June 2012. Over the years, I&amp;rsquo;ve had the opportunity to work with some incredible teams and tackle a variety of projects that have shaped my skills and perspective.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://isaganijaen.com/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://isaganijaen.com/resume/</guid>
      <description>Experience Software Development Senior Analyst Accenture in the Philippines Jun 2022 - Present 路 Worked directly with clients as GNR-Analytics Lead. 路 Applied innovative ideas to drive the automation of Delivery Analytics at the client level using technologies such as clients&#39; internal Business Intelligence Suite, Google&#39;s F1 Engine, Google SQL, Workflow Pipeline, Google App Scripts and performed data analysis using Python and Colab.
System Developer Analyst Accenture in the Philippines Oct 2020 - Jun 2022 路 1 yr 9 mos 路 Perfromed ETL, reports mobilization, dashboard creation, workflow automation, and reporting automation.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
